tutorsweb.com 2016-05-02

# TutorsWeb.com - Find Teachers, Courses Online for FREE & Learn

#### Privacy policy

At TutorsWeb, we take privacy seriously and adhere to United States Federal and State laws that specify guidelines for protection of data and personal information. We do everything to protect you, institutes and organizations connected to us by vigorously resisting attempts to compromise data. In order to give you a clear picture on how we collect data and use it, kindly read the Privacy Policy given below. By registering/accessing our site, you agree and give your consent to collection of data, its use and disclosure of information as mentioned in our Privacy policy.

* * *

#### Information Collected by TutorsWeb

We collect information to provide better service to users. However, you have complete control on the privacy of information you share with us. TutorsWeb does not sell, share or disclose any kind of personal information to third parties without your consent or except as mentioned in our policy or if required by the law to do so.

We may use your information to contact you by telephone, email to inform you about services, get your feedback about services used or provide support on any issues related to services at TutorsWeb.

* * *

#### Other websites

This website may contain links to other organizations, vendors and other web resources that conduct transactions on behalf of TutorsWeb. The websites of our vendors, advertisers and other websites to which we link to may collect information from you when you proceed to their site. TutorsWeb is not responsible for any information collected by our advertisers, vendors or partner organizations when you browse their sites. Please view their privacy policies to know more about information collection and its use

* * *

#### Authorizing you as a TutorsWeb member

After successful registration, you will be required to login into your account for authentication purpose. Your account at TutorsWeb page will include a Profile page that will list all information you have provided during registration. TutorsWeb will publish your First name and Last name with any content you post on TutorsWe

* * *

#### Email

TutorsWeb will use the email registered primarily for communication. You will receive our newsletter, updates and content beneficial to you only if you have opted to receive it during registration process. You can always unsubscribe from such communication if you want to by following the unsubscribing procedure.

* * *

#### Cookie Information

Our website uses cookies to enhance your online experience. A cookie is small text file that is placed on your computer when you browse our website. However, it does not tell us who you are or does not collect any data from your computer. The cookie only provides stately information about your visit to our website.

* * *

#### Policy on Abuse

We are committed to ensure a safe and friendly online community for all our members. TutorsWeb will request all its members to comply with the rules given below.

1\. Do not use website intimidate, verbally abuse, or harass anyone. You should not behave or act in a manner that would cause distress or annoyance to other members

2\. Do not post any content that is inflammatory, religious views, threatening, harassing, obscene, embarrassing or abusive to other members.

3\. Do not disclose any personal information in posts or messages as it will accessible to entire Internet community.

4\. Please be aware of online dangers such as phishing, identity theft and other activities of fraud

* * *

#### Notification of changes in Privacy Policy

TutorsWeb reserves the right to change or update its Privacy Policy whenever it feels the need to. We review our privacy policy on a periodic basis and changes are made as we add new features or services to the website. Hence we request you to periodically view our privacy policy and stay updated.
